The Carleton Hodge collection: books from the library of Carleton Hodge Z7770 .H6
Lilly Library
- B (Box 28)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues: and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. Stereotype edition. Philadelphia: Bible Association of Friends in America, 1844 (Box 53)
  - Bible. Devotional family Bible: with practical and experimental reflections on each verse of the Old and New Testaments, and rich marginal references. By the Rev. Alexander Fletcher D. D. London and New York: Virtue, Emmins & Roberts2 volumes., [1844 or 1845?] (Box 15)
  - Bible. Der Bibel, oder die ganze Heilige Schrift des alten und neuen Testaments. Mit Tsugabe des dritten buchs der Maccabaer und des dritten und vierten buchs Efra, ... Philadelphia: Mentz und Roboudt, 1845 (Box 40)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1845 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongue and with the former translations compared and revised. Stereotype edition. Philadelphia: Bible Association of Friends in America, 1845 (Box 2)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1846 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Illuminated bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues. and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. With marginal readings, references and chronological dates. ... New York: Harper & Brothers, Publishers, 1846 (Box 49)
  - Bible. English version of the Polyglott Bible: containing the old and new testaments, with the marginal readings: together with a copious and original selection of references to parallel and illustrative passages. Exhibited in a manner hitherto unattempted. New York: American and Foreign Bible Society, 1847 (Box 22)
  - Bible. (old testament t.p. missing starts w/chap V,VI signature a2 or page 5 information from new testament t.p.) New testament of our lord and saviour Jesus Christ, the original Greek; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. Hartford: S. Andrus & Son, 1847 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1848 (Box 16)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1848-1849 (N.T. has date of 1849) (Box 11)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. With Canne's marginal references. Together with the Apocrypha and Concordance. To which are added, an index, a table of texts, and what has never before been added, an account of the lives and martyrdoms of the apostles and evangelists. ... stereotyped by James Conner, New York. Hartford: S. Andrus and Son., 1849 (Box 54)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments together with the Apocrypha translated from the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised; with Canne's marginal notes and references. ... Concordance, and the Psalms of David in metre. Philadelphia: Edward W. Miller, 1849 (Box 54)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old testament and the new: according to the commonly received version. New York: American and Foreign Bible Society, 1849-1850. (New Testament dated 1850) (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1850 (Box 15)
  - Bible. Holy Bible; containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. With marginal readings, references, and chronological dates. New York: George Lane & Levi Scott, 1850 (Box 17)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: together with the Apocrypha: translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. With Canne's marginal notes and references. ... Buffalo: Phinney & Co., 1850-1851. (N.T. t.p. imprint 1851) (Box 18)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, together with the Apocrypha: translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. To which is appended, a concordance, the Psalms of David in metre, ... The text conformable to that of the American Bible Society. Philadelphia: I. Kohler, [1850-188?] (Box 51)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society(2 copies same size and same cover)., 1851 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1851 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Kimber & Sharpless' Edition. The holy bible, containing the old and new testaments, together with the Apocrypha: translated from the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised; with Canne's marginal notes and references; to which are added an index, ... Philadelphia: Jesper Harding, 1851 (Box 48)
  - Bible. Kimber & Sharpless' Edition. The holy bible, containing the old and new testaments, together with the Apocrypha: translated from the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised; with Canne's marginal notes and references; to which are added an index, ... Philadelphia: Jesper Harding, 1851 (Box 48)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised, by his majesty's special command. London: G.E. Eyre and W. Spottiswoode, 1853-1854 (New Testament has date of 1854) (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1853-1854 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised, by his majesty's special command. London: G.F. Eyre and W. Spottiswoode, 1854 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1854 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1854 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, together with the Apocrypha: translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. To which is appended, a Concordance, the Psalms of David in Metre, ... Cincinnati: Published by J.A. & U.P. James; stereotyped by A.C. James, 1854 (Box 17)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues: and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1855 (Box 11)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues: and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1855 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, together with Apocrypha: translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. ... Philadelphia: John B. Perry, 1855 (Box 21)
  - Bible. Comprehensive Bible: containing the old and new testaments, according to the authorized version, with the various readings and marginal notes usually printed therewith a general introduction, containing disquisitions... Philological and explanatory notes: ... Philadelphia: Lippincott, Grambo & Co., 1855 (Box 27)
  - Bible. English version of the polyglot bible, containing the old and new testaments; with the marginal readings; together with a copious and original selection of references to parallel and illustrative passages, exhibited in a manner hitherto unattempted. Philadelphia: Lippincott, Grambo & Co., 1855 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1856 (Box 11)
  - Bible. Pictorial bible, being the old and new testaments according to the authorized version: illustrated with more than one thousand engravings, representing the historical events, after celebrated pictures; the landscape scenes, from original drawings, or from authentic engravings; and the subjects of natural history, costume, and antiquities, from the best sources. New York: Robert Sears, 1856 (Box 54)
  - Bible. (O.T. t.p. is missing. And p.7-10 of Genesis missing information from N.T. t.p.) New Testament, according to the authorized version; with the marginal references, and the usual various readings. Also notes; reflections; questions; improved readings; ... by the Rev. Ingram Cobbin, M.A. illustrated with numerous descriptive engravings. [S.l.: s.n., 1856] (Date from a note by Hodge) (Box 27)
  - Bible. (No t.p. in front of O.T. using info from N.T.) New Testament of our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ: translated out of the original Greek; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. With marginal readings, references, and chronological dates. New York: T. Carlton & J. Porter, 1857 (Box 14)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1857 (Box 8)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1857 (Box 36)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society(Bottom half of N.T. page missing), 1857 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1858 (Box 11)
  - Bible. (No t.p. in front of O.T. using info from N.T.) New Testament of our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ, translated out of the original Greek, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1858 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, together with the Apocrypha: translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. To which is appended, a Concordance, the Psalms of David in metere, ... Philadelphia: J.B. Lippincott & Company, 1858 (Box 14)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1859 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Hardings' fine edition. The Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues, together with the Apocrypha, Concordance, and Psalms, and with the former translations... conformable to the original edition of the year of our Lord 1610, and the American Bible Society's Original Standard edition of 1816. Philadelphia: William W. Harding, 1862 (Box 14)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1862 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1863 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues: and with the former translations diligently compared and revised, by his majesty's special command. Oxford: University Press, 1864 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Cottage Bible, and family expositor; containing the old and new testaments, with practical expositions and explanatory notes. By Thomas Williams ... to which are added, the references and marginal readings of the Polyglott Bible, together with ... embellished with maps and engravings. Edited by Rev. William Patton, D. D. Complete in two volumes. Hartford: Printed and Published by Case, Lockwood and Company, 1864 (Box 30)
    - v.1 (Box 30)
    - v.2 (Box 30)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1864 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues: and with former translations diligently compared and revised. Philadelphia: J.B. Lippincott & Co., 1864 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues: and with the former translations diligently compared and revised, by his majesty's special command. Oxford, University Press, 1865-1866. (New Testament with date of 1866) (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the new and old testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1865 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible. Containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1866 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1867 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1867 (Box 30)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues, together with the Apocrypha, Concordance and Psalms, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. Text conformable to the original edition of the year of our Lord 1610, ... Philadelphia: William W. Harding, 1867 (Box 30)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, according to the authorized version; with the marginal references, and the usual various readings. Also notes, reflections... by Rev. Ingram Cobbin. M.A. illustrated with numerous descriptive engravings. Hartford: Case, Lockwood and Company, 1867 (Box 47)
  - Bible. Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1868 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Pronouncing bible. The Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised; ... according to the orthoepy of John Walker. By Israel Alger, Jun. A. M. Pittsburgh: United Presbyterian Board of Publication, 1868 (Box 12)
  - Bible. Comprehensive Bible; containing the old and new testaments, according to the authorized version with the various readings and marginal notes usually printed therewith. A general introduction, containing disquisitions... philological and explanatory notes: a table of contents... an index to the notes, introductions, and concluding remarks. Philadelphia: J.B. Lippincott & Company, 1869 (Box 20)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1869 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1869 (Box 13)
  - Bible. Complete analysis of the Holy Bible: or, how to comprehend holy writ from its own interpretation, containing the whole of the old and new testaments, collected systematically arranged in thirty books; together with an introduction, ... So elaborated and arranged in alphabetical order as to direct at one to any subject required. By Rev. Nathaniel West, D.D. ... New York: A.J. Johnson, Publisher, 1869 (Box 33)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments; translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1870 (Box 17)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1870 (Box 17)
  - Bible. Devotional and practical polyglot family bible, containing the old and new testaments, with the marginal readings, and a full and original selection of references to parallel and illustrative passages, arranged in a manner hitherto unattempted. Together with a concordance, a careful index to the bible, ... Cincinnati, OH: National Publishing Co., 1870 (Box 16)
  - Bible. Devotional family bible containing the old and new testaments according to the most approved copies of the authorized version with practical and experimental reflections on each verse and rich marginal references and readings. By the Rev. Alexander Fletcher, D.D. New York: Virtue and Yorston, [1870?] (Box 53)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1871 (Box 16)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1872 (Box 16)
  - Bible. Die Bibel oder die ganze Heilige Schrift des alten and neuen testaments nach der deutschen uebersetzung D. Martin Luther's. Berlin: Ferlad der Königlikhen Gehrimen Oder Hofbuchbrudere (R. f. Deder), 1872 (Box 19)
  - Bible. Die Bibel oder die ganze Heilige Schrift des alten and neuen testaments. New York: Amerikanishe Bible Gesllschaft, 1872 (Box 40)
  - Bible. Hitchcock's new and complete analysis of the holy bible: or, the whole of the old and new testaments arranged according to subjects in twenty-seven books. On the basis of Matthew Talbot, as improved with indexes, tables, and other valuable matter by Nathaniel West, D.D. ... Word of God. Revised and edited by Rev. Roswell D. Hitchcock, D.D. ... New York: A.J. Johnson, 1872 (Box 33)
  - Bible. Latest illustrated polyglot family bible containing the old and new testaments, together with the Apocrypha: translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. To which are appended... New York and Cincinnati: C.F. Vent, (4 other publ. Locations and publs. Also listed), 1872 (Box 47)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, authorized version, carefully revised with Bagster's references in full. Pittsburgh: United Presbyterian Board of Publication, 1873 (Box 4)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1873-1874 (N.T. has imprint 1873) (Box 17)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1874 (Box 17)
  - Bible. Pictorial home bible, devotional and explanatory: containing the old and new testaments, with the apocrypha, concordance, and marginal references. The text conformable to the standard of the American Bible Society: ... Philadelphia, Cincinnati, Springfield: William Flint and Syracuse, N.T.: Watson Gill and Thompsonville, Conn., Horace King, 1874 (Box 40)
  - Bible. Approved holy Catholic Bible. The Holy bible: containing the entire canonical scriptures, according to the decree of the council of Trent; translated from the Latin Vulgate: diligently compared with the Hebrew, Greek and other editions in divers languages. ... with annotations by the Rev. Dr. Challoner; to which is added the history of the Holy Catholic Bible, ... London and Ontario: Schuyler Smith and Company, [1875?] (Box 41)
  - Bible. Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments: translated out of the original tongues; and with the former translations diligently compared and revised. New York: American Bible Society, 1878 (Box 16)
  - Bible. Hitchcock's new and complete analysis of the holy bible: or, the whole of the old and new testaments arranged according to subjects in twenty-seven books. On the basis of Matthew Talbot, as improved with indexes, tables, and other valuable matter by Nathaniel West, D.D. ... Word of God. Revised and edited by Rev. Roswell D. Hitchcock, D.D., LL.D., ... New York: Alvin J. Johnson Son, and Pittsburg: W.D. Cummings, and Chicago: E.P. Kingsley, 1878 (Box 33)
  - Bible. Holman's edition. The Holy Bible, containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised; with complete concordance. Embracing every passage of scripture in the largest editions. Apocrypha and Psalms. Philadelphia: A.J. Holman & Co., 1879 (Box 20)
  - Bible. Neue Illustrirte familien bibel, für häusliche erbauung und belehrung. Nthaltend das alte und neue testaments, mit den … mit einer einleitung von Rev. A. Martin … Cincinnati: F.? M.? Dillie & Co., 187? (Date from verso of t.p. when it was entered according to an Act of Congress, but I can't read the last number of the date) (Box 43)
  - Bible. Standard edition. The Holy Bible containing the old and new testaments, translated out of the original tongues, and with the former translations diligently compared and revised; with concordance and psalms of David in meter. The text conformable to the Oxford and the American Bible Society's standard editions. Chicago: David C. Cook, [1879-1882] (Dates are from the verso of t.p. when they were entered according to an act of congress, n.t. has 1882) (Box 23)